{
    "subject": "resource/Elinor_Ostrom",
    "predicate": "ontology/award",
    "object": "resource/Nobel_Memorial_Prize_in_Economic_Sciences",
    "human_readable": "Elinor Ostrom was awarded the Nobel Memorial Prize in Economic Sciences.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.987381637096405,
            "question": "When was Elinor Ostrom awarded the Nobel Memorial Prize in Economic Sciences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9214143753051758,
            "question": "Who was awarded the Nobel Memorial Prize in Economic Sciences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8828643560409546,
            "question": "In what field did Elinor Ostrom receive a Nobel Prize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8192427158355713,
            "question": "Who were some of the other recipients of the Nobel Memorial Prize in Economic Sciences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7860932946205139,
            "question": "What prize did Elinor Ostrom win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6743813753128052,
            "question": "What are some of Elinor Ostrom's major contributions to economics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4321688413619995,
            "question": "What is significant about Elinor Ostrom's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35136938095092773,
            "question": "What are some key concepts associated with Elinor Ostrom's research?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34132394194602966,
            "question": "How did Elinor Ostrom's background influence her work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25136563181877136,
            "question": "What impact did Elinor Ostrom's work have on her field?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Elinor Ostrom was awarded the Nobel Memorial Prize in Economic Sciences.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8046_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Elinor Ostrom's background influence her work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8046_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key concepts associated with Elinor Ostrom's research?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8046_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is significant about Elinor Ostrom's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8046_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8046_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8046_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8046_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8046_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8046_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8046_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8046_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8046_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8046_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8046_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as all four files mention that Elinor Ostrom received the Nobel Memorial Prize in Economic Sciences."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}